Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010 TJU.2010.01.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Trip Files, 1981-2010; V.
  - Domestic trips, 1983-2008; 2.
    - Lancaster and Dauphin Counties: Farms, Chamber of Commerce, April 1, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 30)
    - Dauphin and Hershey: Conrail, GOP Breakfast, Realtors, April 7, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 31)
    - Hershey, New Cumberland: Township supervisors, April 29, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 32)
    - Mifflintown: Anne Anstine Memorial, June 6, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 33)
    - Central and Northeastern Pennslvania: Town halls, July 1-3, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 34)
    - Lackawanna and Dauphin Counties: Children's health, August 1, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 35)
    - Ohio, Philadelphia: Construction, Ohio State University, August 13-15, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 36)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Republican State Committee, September 26-27, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 37)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Chamber of Commerce, United Defense, October 6, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 38)
    - Lancaster and Delaware Counties, Philadelphia: Religious persecution, November 24, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 39)
    - Berks, York, Cumberland, Dauphin Counties: CAS Breakfast, Religious leaders, October 27, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 40)
    - Lebanon, Dauphin, Union, Montour: CAS, Allenwoon Federal Prison, Education, December 4-5, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 41)
    - Lackawanna, Luzerne, Schuylkill, Montgomery: Judge Caputo, December 15, 1997 (Box 711, Folder 1)
    - Harrisburg: Ridge/Schweiker announcement, January 14, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 2)
    - New Cumberland, Middletown, Lancaster: State committee, CAS, January 22, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 3)
    - Middletown, Pittsburgh, Altoona, Erie, Scranton, Bethlehem: Announcement tour, February 2, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 4)
    - Hershey, Carlisle, Lebanon, Lancaster: Steelworkers, Town meetings, February 9, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 5)
    - New York: Republican dinner, February 11, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 6)
    - York, Hanover, Adams, Dauphin Counties: CAS, Town meetings, February 13, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 7)
    - Harrisburg: Republican State Committee, February 13-14, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 8)
    - Dauphin, Lycoming, Schuylkill: Alex Grass, CAS, March 24, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 9)
    - Harrisburg, Mechanicsburg, McConnellsburg, Chambersburg: Farms, High school, Abstinence, March 30, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 10)
    - Gettysburg, York, Lancaster, Myerstown: Religious persecution, Family services, April 3, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 11)
    - Dauphin County, Carlisle, Lancaster, Wyomissing, Philadelphia: Flat tax, Transportation, Abstinence, Army Museum, April 15, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 12)
    - State College, Blair County, Cambria County: Community leaders, Abstinence, April 24, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 13)
    - Harrisburg: Sportsmen, AFL-CIO, CAS, Republican Caucus, Abstinence, April 27, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 14)
    - Dauphin, Pittsburgh: American Legion, VA Medical Center, May 4, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 15)
    - Red Lion, Harrisburg, Lancaster: Media, Abstinence, May 15, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 16)
    - Harrisburg, Gettysburg: Light rail, Media, PSEA summer leadership, July 27, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 17)
    - Northumberland and Snyder Counties: Town meetings, August 17, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 18)
    - Harrisburg, Philadelphia: Private schools, Flood warning, Building and construction, August 17-18, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 19)
    - Scranton, Tunkhannock, Dushore, Bloomsburg: Town meetings, August 19, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 20)
    - Williamsport, Clinton County, State College: Town meetings, CAS, August 24-25, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 21)
    - Central and Western Pennsylvania: Town meetings, Veterans, August 26-27, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 22)
    - York, Hershey: Media, Republican State Committee, October 2-3, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 23)
    - Delaware County, Lancaster: Cabrini College, Domestic violence, Amish, October 5, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 24)
    - Lycoming, Luzerne, Lackawanna Counties: CAS, VA Medical Center, October 13, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 25)
    - Dauphin, Lancaster, Lebanon: Plant tour, Cedar Cliff High School, October 19, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 26)
    - Huntingdon, Blair, Erie, Fayette, Allegheny, Indiana Counties, Philadelphia, October 20-22, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 27)
    - Pottstown, Harrisburg, Erie, Villanova: High school, City committee, October 27, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 28)
    - Harrisburg, Philadelphia, Avoca, Johnstown, Pittsburgh: Rallies, November 2, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 29)
    - Wilkes-Barre, Harrisburg, Middletown: Dairy farmers, Veterans, February 16, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 30)
    - Philadelphia, Middletown, Allentown, Marion Station: National Guard, May 17, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 31)
    - Factoryville, Harrisburg: Dairy farmers, Children, July 6, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 32)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: Colleges, Farmers, Building and construction, August 10, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 33)
    - Lebanon, Wilkes-Barre, Allentown, Philadelphia, Coatesville, August 15-20, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 34)
    - Lemoyne, Harrisburg: Republican State Committee, October 1-2, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 35)
    - Northwestern Pennsylvania: Town meetings, October 16, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 36)
    - Town meetings, October 1999 (Box 711, Folder 37)
    - Sunbury, Williamsport, State College: Town meetings, Penn State, November 4, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 38)
    - Harrisburg, Camp Hill: YMCA, Republican State Committee, January 21-22, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 39)
    - Lehigh and Dauphin Counties: Tobyhanna Army Depot, VA Clinic, Drugs, April 3, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 40)
    - Carlisle, Harrisburg: Army heritage, Republican State Committee, May 19-20, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 41)
    - Bethlehem, Scranton, Summit, Harrisburg: Health, Medical errors, June 12, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 42)
    - Allentown, Wilkes-Barre, Harrisburg: Script-Fast, VA Medical Center, July 24, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 43)
    - Quakertown, Bethlehem, West Lawn, Lancaster, York: Media, High schools, Governor Bush, September 5, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 44)
    - Harrisburg: Republican State Committee, September 23, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 45)
    - Allentown, Avoca, Scranton, Dunmore, Camp Hill: Prison, Clinic, Harper Collins, October 10, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 46)
    - Reading, Lancaster: CAS, Emergency shelter, Town meetings, October 15, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 47)
    - Pennsylvania cities, Ohio: Book signings, College students, October 30 - November 2, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 48)
    - Harrisburg: Juvenile detention center, PA Newsmakers, November 13, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 49)
    - Dauphin County, Lancaster: High school, Bar Association, Amish youth, December 1, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 50)
    - Harrisburg, Philadelphia: Religious leaders, Book signing, December 13-14, 2000 (Box 711, Folder 51)
    - Hershey, Harrisburg: Steelworkers, Cable, Police crime lab, February 5, 2001 (Box 711, Folder 52)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: Maglev, Sertoma Club, State Committee, February 9-10, 2001 (Box 711, Folder 53)
    - Scranton, Harrisburg: CAS, Firefighters and emergency response, April 2, 2001 (Box 711, Folder 54)
    - Exeter, Wilkes-Barre, Harrisburg: Republican leadership, CAS, YWCA, April 30, 2001 (Box 711, Folder 55)
    - Lancaster and Montgomery Counties: Safe Harbor Power, Blind, May 18, 2001 (Box 711, Folder 56)
    - Pittsburgh, Dauphin County: CAS, Farms, Carnegie Mellon, Jewish Community Center, May 29-31, 2001 (Box 711, Folder 57)
    - Central and Northeastern Pennsylvania: CAS, Veterans, Ammunition, June 11, 2001 (Box 711, Folder 58)
    - Northern Pennsylvania: CAS, Town meetings, Hospital, July 2-3, 2001 (Box 712, Folder 1)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Town meetings, Fulton County Medical Center, August 14-15, 2001 (Box 712, Folder 2-4)
    - Central Pennsylvania: September 11, Republican State Committee, September 28-29, 2001 (Box 712, Folder 5)
    - Gettysburg, Harrisburg: Swearing-in of Mark Schweiker, October 5, 2001 (Box 712, Folder 6)
    - Harrisburg: Pennsylvania Business Roundtable, October 10, 2001 (Box 712, Folder 7)
    - Reading, Lancaster: Town meetings, CAS, Emergency shelter, October 15, 2001 (Box 712, Folder 8)
    - Dauphin County: CAS, Three Mile Island, November 12, 2001 (Box 712, Folder 9)
    - Scranton, Harrisburg, Middletown: CAS, Airport, January 28, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 10)
    - Harrisburg: Weapons of mass destruction, Republican State Committee, February 8-9, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 11)
    - Dauphin, Adams Counties: CAS, Steelworkers, McKelvey Foundation, February 25, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 12)
    - Eastern and Central Pennsylvania: CAS, Community prevention, Press, April 8, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 13)
    - Allentown, Harrisburg, York: Media, May 6, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania cities: Korean War veterans, CAS, Media, May 28-30, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 15)
    - Gettysburg, Chambersburg, Harrisburg: Republican State Committee, Town meetings, June 28-29, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania Counties: Town meetings, July 1-3, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 17)
    - Reading, Lancaster, York: Town meetings, Police association, July 15, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania cities: Town meetings, August 26-28, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 19)
    - Pottsville, Dauphin County, Philadelphia: Republican State Committee, Veterans, September 27-29, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 20)
    - Lebanon, Harrisburg: Town meeting, Transportation, September 30, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 21)
    - Philadelphia, Harrisburg: Education, Gekas, October 15, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 22)
    - New York: Humpty Dumpty Institute to UN, October 24-25, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 23)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: CAS, November 12, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 24)
    - Lancaster, York, Carlisle: CAS, Army War College, York College, November 18, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 25)
    - Hershey, Allentown, Fogelsville: Fred Anton, County Commissioners, November 26, 2002 (Box 712, Folder 26)
    - Harrisburg: Christian leaders, Open house, January 21, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 27)
    - Harrisburg: Republican State Committee, February 7-8, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 28)
    - Scranton, Lancaster: CAS, Chamber of Commerce, March 3, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 29)
    - Reading, Lancaster, Harrisburg, Altoona: Abstinence, CAS, March 10, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 30)
    - Lancaster, Harrisburg, Mechanicsburg: Gambling, Airport, Naval Depot, March 17, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 31)
    - Pittsburgh, Harrisburg: Abstinence, Lawyers, Republican Caucus, March 24, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 32)
    - Hershey, Media: Construction, Garry Sutton Show, April 2-3, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 33)
    - Harrisburg, York: Federal judges, Health, United Defense, Colleges, April 7, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 34)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: CAS, Town meetings, April 14-18, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 35)
    - Pennsylvania Cities, Boston: CAS, Abstinence, Mitt Romney, April 21-22, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 36)
    - Chester and Lancaster Counties: Airport, Republican Committee, April 28, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 37)
    - Harrisburg, York, Ephrata, Philadelphia: SARS, Interviews, CAS, May 2, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 38)
    - Harrisburg, Lancaster: Republican Caucus, Lincoln Day Dinner, May 5, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 39)
    - Pittsburgh, Frackville: CAS, Appalachian Regional Commission, May 29-30, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 40)
    - Harrisburg, Altoona: News conference, CAS, June 2, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 41)
    - Harrisburg, Hersey, Duncannon, Carlisle: Republican officials, June 23, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 42)
    - Scranton, Harrisburg: CAS, Firefighters, Sportsman, July 7, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 43)
    - Central and Northeastern Pennsylvania: GOP luncheons, Farms, First responders, August 6-8, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 44)
    - Central Pennsylvania: First responders, Republican leaders, August 20-21, 2003 (Box 712, Folder 45)
    - Harrisburg, Camp Hill: Republican State Committee, September 19-21, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 1)
    - Luzerne County, Hershey: Autism, Gas, Manufacturers, September 22, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 2)
    - Southeastern and Central Pennsylvania: Flooding, Hospital, October 24, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 3)
    - Lehigh, Northampton, Dauphin Counties: Town meeting, Teen pregnancy, October 27, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 4)
    - Dauphin County: Judicial candidates, CAS, Bush campaign, November 3, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 5)
    - Lycoming and Clinton Counties, State College: CAS, GOP meeting, November 7, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 6)
    - Lancaster: Mayor, Press conference, City Medical Society, November 10, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 7)
    - Wilkes-Barre, Mechanicsburg, Harrisburg: CAS, Kennedy assassination, November 17, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 8)
    - Landsdowne, Washington Crossing, Harrisburg: PA Medical Society, Schools, December 1, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 9)
    - New York City, Harrisburg, Philadelphia: CAS, Andy McKelvey, December 9, 2003 (Box 713, Folder 10)
    - Pennsylvania Cities: Announcements, Republican State Committee, January 8-10, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 11)
    - Leola, Harrisburg, Camp Hill: Agri-business, PSEA, Nurses Coalition, January 17, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 12)
    - Lancaster, York, Carlisle, Harrisburg: Republican State Committee, Manufacturing, January 23-24, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia, Harrisburg: Elections, Abstinence, February 16, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 14)
    - Allentown, Bethlehem, Harrisburg: Jewish leaders, Mayor Reed, March 1, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 15)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Interviews, CAS, Dairy farmers, March 17, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 16)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Penn State, CAS, Chamber of Commerce, SEIU, April 14, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 17)
    - Boston, Pennsylvania cities: Aviation, CAS, Highways, Agriculture, March 22, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 18)
    - New York, Central Pennsylvania: CAS, Aviation, Health, March 28-29, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 19)
    - Southeastern Pennsylvania: Judiciary confirmations, Taxes, April 15, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 20)
    - Philadelphia, Harrisburg, Hershey: President Bush, Township supervisors, April 19, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania cities: Medicaid, Republican Committee, Hunters, News, April 21-22, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania airports, April 26, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 23)
    - Cumberland County: Pennsylvanians for Effective Government, May 11, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 24)
    - Harrisburg, Chambersburg: Keystone Rural Health Center, May 17, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 25)
    - Harrisburg: Political Action Committee for Education, State Committee, June 4-5, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 26)
    - Berks and Cumberland Counties: CAS, Higher education, AFSCME, June 7, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 27)
    - Bethlehem, Allentown, Lancaster, Lemoyne: Judges, CAS, June 28, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania cities: Manufacturing, PSEA, UPMC, Military, CAS, July 26-28, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 29)
    - Virginia, Harrisburg: Education Finance Council, American Legion, Veterans, July 16, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania cities: CAS, Building and Trades Council, Dairy, Teen suicide, August 9-12, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 31)
    - Wayne, Harrisburg: CAS, Fred Anton, August 13, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 32)
    - State College, Somerset, Pittsburgh, Meadowbrook: Agriculture, Flight 93, Coal, Town meeting, August 18-19, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 33)
    - Lancaster: Air show, August 28, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 34)
    - New Jersey, Hershey, Middletown: AFL-CIO, Aviation, August 31, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 35)
    - Philadelphia, Harrisburg: CAS, Caucus, September 10-12, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 36)
    - Scranton, Moosic, Harrisburg: CAS, FEMA, Farms, September 27, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 37)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: Health, Editorial boards, Women, October 14, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 38)
    - Harrisburg, Philadelphia: State Troopers, CAS, Public Service Award, October 20, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 39)
    - Lancaster, York, Philadelphia: Press conferences, Aerospace, October 29, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 40)
    - Pennsylvania cities: Aviation, News conferences, November 1, 2004 (Box 713, Folder 41)
    - Penn State: President Bush, June 14, 2005 (Box 713, Folder 42)
    - Dauphin and Cumberland Counties: CAS, Roundtable with reporters, November 28, 2005 (Box 713, Folder 43)
    - Pennsylvania cities: Prison reform, Republican leaders, August 28-31, 2005 (Box 713, Folder 44)
    - Avoca, Harrisburg, Altoona: CAS, Flood recovery efforts, July 6-7, 2006 (Box 713, Folder 45)
    - Pittsburgh, Camp Hill, Middletown, Philadelphia: Republican State Committee, Hospital, September 15-16, 2006 (Box 713, Folder 46)
    - Lancaster, Harrisburg: Fundraiser, Marshall College, Fred Anton, September 18, 2006 (Box 713, Folder 47)
    - Lycoming and Schuylkill Counties: CAS, Republican leaders, Business leaders, October 6, 2006 (Box 713, Folder 48)
    - Central and Southeastern Pennsylvania: Republican candidates, Medical society, October 20, 2006 (Box 713, Folder 49)
    - Wilkes-Barre, Hershey: CAS, Floods, News, Medical center, December 11, 2006 (Box 713, Folder 50)
    - Harrisburg, Camp Hill, Scranton: Giant food stores, CAS, Medical, February 21, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 51)
    - Reading, Lancaster, York: CAS, Criminal activity, March 12, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 52)
    - Scranton, Eynon, Williamsport: CAS, General Dynamics, Health, Internet safety, April 2, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 53)
    - Dauphin County, Lancaster, Lemoyne: Township supervisors, Courthouse, April 23, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 54)
    - State College, Blair and Cambria Counties: Republican State Committee, Farms, May 4, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 55)
    - Avoca, Harrisburg, Hazelton: CAS, PA Newsmakers, SEIU, June 25, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 56)
    - York, Camp Hill, Hershey: Cable, Occupational safety, June 29, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 57)
    - Dauphin County: Federal Courthouse, July 7, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 58)
    - Central Pennsylvania: Town meetings, CAS, Republican leaders, August 6-9, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 59)
    - Harrisburg: Rail, La Salle University, Republican State Committee, September 7, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 60)
    - Central Pennsylvania, Philadelphia: CAS, Medical Center, Colleges, Biotech, October 8, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 61)
    - Allentown, Mechanicsburg, Harrisburg: CAS, GOP rally, Medical center, November 5, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 62)
    - Central and Eastern Pennsylvania: CAS, Solomon Creek, November 20, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 63)
    - Philadelphia, Collegeville, Dauphin County: Lancaster homeowners, December 10, 2007 (Box 713, Folder 64)
    - Moosic, Scranton, Harrisburg: Farm show, CAS, Medical college, January 8, 2008 (Box 713, Folder 65)